whofish.org 2010-06-24

# WhoFish.org - Home - Local Events and Activities

WhoFish.org is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the WhoFish.org Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the WhoFish.org website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

WhoFish.org currently only collects your e-mail address when you either submit a listing(Contributor), or Subscribe to a service(Subscriber).

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by WhoFish.org. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by WhoFish.org for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the WhoFish.org Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through WhoFish.org public Listings, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: WhoFish.org does not read any of your private online communications.

WhoFish.org encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from WhoFish.org so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. WhoFish.org is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the WhoFish.org and WhoFish.org family of Web sites.

Use of your Personal Information

WhoFish.org collects and uses your personal information to operate the WhoFish.org Web site and deliver the services you have requested. WhoFish.org also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from WhoFish.org and its affiliates. WhoFish.org may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Recipients may "unsubscribe" at anytime.

WhoFish.org does not sell, rent or lease its Subscriber/Contributor lists to third parties. WhoFish.org may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, WhoFish.org may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to WhoFish.org, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

WhoFish.org does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

WhoFish.org keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within WhoFish.org, in order to determine what WhoFish.org services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within WhoFish.org to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

WhoFish.org Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on WhoFish.org or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of WhoFish.org; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of WhoFish.org, or the public.

Use of Business Email Lists

As a value added service, WhoFish.org maintains separate email lists submitted by our clients which are not collected by WhoFish.org. These lists are solely for use by the submitting client and will not be used in any way without their consent and direction. As with our subscription-based groups, a recipient may "unsubscribe" at anytime. 

Use of Cookies

The WhoFish.org Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize WhoFish.org pages, or register with WhoFish.org site or services, a cookie helps WhoFish.org to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same WhoFish.org Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the WhoFish.org features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the WhoFish.org services or Web sites you visit.

Security of your Personal Information

WhoFish.org secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. WhoFish.org secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

WhoFish.org will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. WhoFish.org encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how WhoFish.org is protecting your information.

Contact Information

WhoFish.org welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that WhoFish.org has not adhered to this Statement, please contact WhoFish.org at [info@whofish.org](mailto:info@whofish.org). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
